The way that the system currently functions
is built on traditions and the way that
things have always been. It's an online
collaborative decision-making tool, which
basically means that if you have many
people that want to discuss proposed
arguments, decide, vote on things together -
they no longer have to meet in the
same physical space - often that would be
impossible because there's too many of
them or they are too geographically
spread out. We have been using Citizen
OS for a simple organizational task
where we need our supervisory board
members, who are around the world
sometimes and not always physically
available, to review our internal policy
documents. The only way for us to move
forward as a civilization is to learn to
really make use of that new quality
of connectedness. Citizen OS enables that.
You can bring a big number of people, you
can decide on things, petitions or
decisions or documents. For a
non-profit organization, for a civic
movement, for a village municipality. Up
to the level of a national
government or even the citizens of a
planet. There's no upper limit
other than the planet. We are part of
democracy festivals network, so that
means that
In our  festival, we hope to
develop opinion culture in Estonia.
Citizen OS could help us on a new
level, to achieve better quality
discussions in opinion festival. It's a
flavour of things to come. It
shows us what technology enables in
the information society where you can
actually get the participation of big,
big numbers of people to jointly come
together and change things.